Topical files 1
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Topical files 1, 2.1.9.4
  - Major General Herbert Darque [Documents pertaining to Air Force Air Defense System Testing; Containing maps, diagrams, and photographs [some originals with copies]; Front and back of pages number a total of 25 [missing pages 1/2 and 21/22], 1932- 1941; 34 (Box 1613)
    - Note[PDF]: Verso: Page 20: showing the flow of telephon traffic. The "ridge-lines" on the telephone mape deterine the extant boundary. 34. Filter areas.- In each region two or more filter areas were set up to prevent overloading of any one filter board with messages...[Original plate from page attached], 19
    - Note[PDF]: Page 23: Plate 19. Pursuit Officer on balcony of old New York Information Center.; Plate 20. Radio officer on balcony of old New York Information Center. [Orginal plates attached], 20
    - Note[PDF]: Verso: Page 24: Personnel in Test; 39. Participating Units.- Units and organization participating in the test will include the following: a. Civilians (1) Forty thousand observers at 1800 observation posts, supplied by State Defense Councils, 21
    - Note[PDF]: Page 25: f. Coast Artillery. (1) 369th A. A. Regiment, Boston, Mass. (2) Provisional Brigade of A. A. consisting of the 62nd C. A., 71st C. A., and 122nd C. A. Battalion of New York[Original plate from page attached], 22
  - Faye Dean, circa 1970s; 35 (Box 1613)
    - Faye Dean L04-3250, 1
  - Desert News, 1964; 36 (Box 1613)
    - [Painting of Lowell Thomas in Alaska], 1
  - Walt Disney, undated; 37 (Box 1613)
    - [Man holding a frame, Walt Disney Picture in the background], 1
  - Dogs, 1947- 1951; 38 (Box 1613)
    - Duke--Father of Pirate, 1
    - Vickie--Mother of Pirate, 2
    - Pirate's family, 3
  - Dan Edwards, undated; 39 (Box 1613)
    - To Dan Edwards--a gallant soldier in war, but, an even braver citizen in peace Herbert [?], 1
  - Sverre and Alf Engen, circa 1960s; 40 (Box 1613)
    - Alf Engen's youngest -John-and bride, 1
    - Note: Alf Engen's youngest -John-and bride [Image holder], 2
  Box 1614
- Topical files 1, 2.1.9.4
  - Farm, 1935; 1 (Box 1614)
    - Note[PDF]: November 25th, 1935. Mr. Lowell Thomas; Hotel Waldorf-Astoria; New York, NY; Monsieur, Veuillez trouver ei-joint la photgraphie de l'esquisse "Tete de Quakeresse" que vous avez remarquee, 1
    - Photograph of painting of woman contained with letter, 2
    - Verso: Murray K. Keyes, Photographer of paintings and art objects, New York, 2-verso
  - Harrison Finch, circa 1960s; 2 (Box 1614)
    - [Harrison Finch: Stewardesses ], 1
    - [Harrison Finch: Stewardesses from different airlines and two men in suits], 2
    - [Harrison Finch: Stewardesses ], 3
    - [Harrison Finch: Stewardesses ], 4
    - [Harrison Finch: Stewardesses from different airlines], 5
    - [Harrison Finch: Stewardesses], 6
  - Flag, undated; 3 (Box 1614)
    - [Man holding flag], 1
  - Lugg Foeger [color photograph], 1979; 4 (Box 1614)
    - Ski incline 1979., 1
    - Verso: Ski incline 1979., 1-verso
  - Malcolm Forbes and Lowell Thomas, 1980; 5 (Box 1614)
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting down with Malcolm Forbes], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with another man. Malcolm Forbes standing next to him], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting and talking with Malcolm Forbes], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas with Malcolm Forbes and group of men], 4
  - Doris Fox, undated; 6 (Box 1614)
    - [Doris Fox in dress], 1
  - Paul Fox, 1958; 7 (Box 1614)
    - Paul Fox; 1958, 1
    - Verso: Paul Fox; 1958, 1-verso
  - Gretchen and Donald Fraser, undated; 8 (Box 1614)
    - Redfern, Canada; Season's Greetings Gretchen, Don, and Bill Fraser, 1
    - Holiday Joy; Thanksgiving and Christmas; Gretchen & Don Fraser, 2
    - Gretchen & Don-Sun Valley, 3
  - Freedom Award letters, 1977; 9 (Box 1614)
    - America's #1 Ambassador at large; Congratulations re Freedom Award; Larry, 1
    - Verso: America's #1 Ambassador at large; Congratulations re Freedom Award; Larry, 1-verso
  - GAF Corporations formerly Sawyers Inc., 1962- 1974; 10 (Box 1614)
    - [GAF Corporations formerly Sawyers Inc.: Miniature models of international landmarks], 1
    - [GAF Corporations formerly Sawyers Inc.: Miniature models of international landmarks], 2
    - [GAF Corporations formerly Sawyers Inc.: Miniature models of international landmarks], 3
    - [GAF Corporations formerly Sawyers Inc.: Woman looking at miniature model of African boab tree], 4
    - [GAF Corporations formerly Sawyers Inc.: Miniature models of the Seven Wonders of the World], 5
    - [GAF Corporations formerly Sawyers Inc.: Lowell Thomas standing with three other men], 6
    - [GAF Corporations formerly Sawyers Inc.: Lowell Thomas looking at papers with another man], 7
    - [GAF Corporations formerly Sawyers Inc.: Lowell Thomas standing with two other men], 8
    - [GAF Corporations formerly Sawyers Inc.: Lowell Thomas sitting with three other men at dining table], 9
    - [GAF Corporations formerly Sawyers Inc.: Lowell Thomas standing with two other men], 10
    - [GAF Corporations formerly Sawyers Inc.: Lowell Thomas standing with three other men], 11
    - [GAF Corporations formerly Sawyers Inc.: Lowell Thomas standing with two other men], 12
  - John Galbreath, 1978 - 1980; 11 (Box 1614)
    - Wishing you the special joy that only Christmas brings. The Galbreaths, Liz and Dan, Laurie, Lizanna, and Squire, 1
    - Verso: [inside] Please come back and see us soon - you are two very special people that we count as out blessings, 1-verso
  - General Motors Corporation, undated; 12 (Box 1614)
    - [Portrait of a man. From General Motors Corporation], 1
  - Norman Gladney, 1977 - 1981; 13 (Box 1614)
    - [Norman Gladney: Close-up of Lowell Thomas], 1
    - [Norman Gladney: Close-up of Lowell Thomas], 2
    - [Norman Gladney: Close-up of Lowell Thomas], 3
    - [Norman Gladney: Close-up of Lowell Thomas], 4
    - [Norman Gladney: Close-up of Lowell Thomas], 5
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1]"World of Lowell Thomas" Program Description: World's Best Known Reporter/Adventurer Featured in Exclusive New Radio Series, 6
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2] Biographical Information, 7
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3] Biographical Information, 8
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 4] Biographical Information, 9
    - Note[PDF]: "World of Lowell Thomas" Program Description: World's Best Known Reporter/Adventurer Featured in Exclusive New Radio Series, 10
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2] Biographical Information, 11
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3] Biographical Information, 12
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 4] Biographical Information, 13
    - Note[PDF]: "World of Lowell Thomas" Program Description: World's Best Known Reporter/Adventurer Featured in Exclusive New Radio Series, 14
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2] Biographical Information, 15
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3] Biographical Information, 16
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 4] Biographical Information, 17
    - Note[PDF]: "World of Lowell Thomas" Program Description: World's Best Known Reporter/Adventurer Featured in Exclusive New Radio Series, 18
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2] Biographical Information, 19
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3] Biographical Information, 20
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 4] Biographical Information, 21
    - Note[PDF]: "World of Lowell Thomas" Program Description: World's Best Known Reporter/Adventurer Featured in Exclusive New Radio Series, 22
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2] Biographical Information, 23
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3] Biographical Information, 24
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 4] Biographical Information, 25
  - Golf and golf carts, undated; 14 (Box 1614)
    - Note[PDF]: Lowell Thomas; Golf Course [drawing], 1
    - [Aerial view of golf course], 2
  - Golf Hall of Fame, 1965 - 1979; 15 (Box 1614)
    - [From Golf Hall of Fame: Marching band lined up on either side outside of building, man swinging a golf club], 1
  - Golf scorecards, 1954 June 12; 16 (Box 1614)
    - Note[PDF]: [Golf scorecard], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Golf scorecard], 2
  - Joyce Graves, 1970- 1975; 17 (Box 1614)
    - Joyce Graves [address] Taken at Garst Musem Sunday August 1 ,1971, 1
    - Verso: Joyce Graves [address] Taken at Garst Musem Sunday August 1 ,1971, 1-verso
    - Joyce Graves [address] Born 2-14-57; 8th Grade, 2
    - Verso: Joyce Graves [address] Born 2-14-57; 8th Grade, 2-verso
    - Joyce Graves [address] 14 years of Age., 3
    - Verso: Joyce Graves [address] 14 years of Age., 3-verso
    - To Grandfather Thomas, Thanks for being such a wonderful person. Love, Joyce Graves Holland High School Class of 1975, 4
    - Verso: To Grandfather Thomas, Thanks for being such a wonderful person. Love, Joyce Graves Holland High School Class of 1975, 4-verso
    - Note: Dear Grandfather Thomas, After spending a month in Alaska I can see why it has attracted you so much, 5
    - Verso: P.S.-Thank you for being an inspiration in my life, 5-verso
  - Carl Gray, undated; 18 (Box 1614)
    - [Carl Gray on skiis], 1
  - Greenville, 1974 June; 19 (Box 1614)
    - June 16 1974 [Greenville, people outside building], 1
    - Verso: June 16 1974, 1-verso
    - June 16-1974 [Greenville, Two people looking out over village], 2
    - Verso: June 16-1974, 2-verso
  - Hall of Fame [aviation], 1974; 20 (Box 1614)
    - [From Hall of Fame Aviation:]WWI Ace George Vaughn; Sopwith Camel "rollout" 12-14-74, 1
    - Verso: WWI Ace George Vaughn; Sopwith Camel "rollout" 12-14-74, 1-verso
    - [From Hall of Fmae Aviation:]WWI Ace George Vaughn making brief remarks prior to Sopwith Camel "rollout" 12-14-74, 2
    - Verso: WWI Ace George Vaughn making brief remarks prior to Sopwith Camel "rollout" 12-14-74, 2-verso
    - [From Hall of Fame Aviation:]WWI Ace George Vaughn taking a photo of the Sopwith Camel during "rollout." 12-14-74, 3
    - Verso: WWI Ace George Vaughn taking a photo of the Sopwith Camel during "rollout." 12-14-74, 3-verso
    - [From Hall of Fame Aviation:]Talking with Mr. and Mrs. Harold Miller of Dayton, Ohio. Mrs. Miller is the niece of the Wright Brothers. Prior to "rollout" of Sopwith Camel., 4
    - Verso: Talking with Mr. and Mrs. Harold Miller of Dayton, Ohio. Mrs. Miller is the niece of the Wright Brothers. Prior to "rollout" of Sopwith Camel., 4-verso
    - [From Hall of Fame Aviation:]Talking with Colonel Bernie Bass, commander of the Air Force Museum, 5
    - Verso: Talking with Colonel Bernie Bass, commander of the Air Force Museum, 5-verso
    - [From Hall of Fame Aviation:]Snoopy and Red Baron at Sopwith Camel "rollout" 12-14-74, 6
    - Verso: Snoopy and Red Baron at Sopwith Camel "rollout" 12-14-74, 6-verso
    - Aviation Hall of Fame Enshrinees at Wright Memorial. L to R: C.L. "Kelly" Johnson, Leigh Wade, John Northrop, C.R. Smith, and T. Claude Ryam. 12-14-74, 7
    - Verso: Aviation Hall of Fame Enshrinees at Wright Memorial. L to R: C.L. "Kelly" Johnson, Leigh Wade, John Northrop, C.R. Smith, and T. Claude Ryam. 12-14-74, 7-verso
    - [From Hall of Fame Aviation:]"Rollout" of Sopwith Camel, 12-14-74, on apron of Air Force Museum., 8
    - Verso: "Rollout" of Sopwith Camel, 12-14-74, on apron of Air Force Museum., 8-verso
    - Aviation Hall of Fame Enshrinees at Wright Memorial. L to R: C.L. "Kelly" Johnson, Leigh Wade, John Northrup, C.R. Smith, and T. Claude Ryan. 12-14-74, 9
    - Verso: Aviation Hall of Fame Enshrinees at Wright Memorial. L to R: C.L. "Kelly" Johnson, Leigh Wade, John Northrup, C.R. Smith, and T. Claude Ryan. 12-14-74, 9-verso
    - [From Hall of Fame Aviation:]WWI Ace George Vaughn; Sopwith Camel "rollout" 12-14-74, 10
    - Verso: WWI Ace George Vaughn; Sopwith Camel "rollout" 12-14-74, 10-verso
  - Henry Hamilton [includes color photograph], 1957; 21 (Box 1614)
    - [Lowell Thomas at microphone with Henry Hamilton], 1
    - [Portrait of Henry Hamilton], 2
  - Helicopter, 1953 - 1954; 22 (Box 1614)
    - [Helicopter], 1
    - Verso: L. Thomas; Los Angeles Airways, inc., 1-verso
  - History As You Heard It by Lowell Thomas, 1957; 23 (Box 1614)
    - [Window display of L.T.'s bookm History as You Heard It], 1
    - Note[PDF]: Homemaker Harmonies WIBX - 950 - CBS in Utica; The new book HISTORY AS YOU HEARD IT by Lowell Thomas is one of the outstanding books of the year, 2
  - Marshall Hoag, 1981; 24 (Box 1614)
    - [Marshall Hoag: Older lady sitting and eating apples], 1
    - [Marshall Hoag: Close-up of older lady], 2
    - [Marhsall Hoag: Older lady standing in front of fireplace], 3
    - [Marshall Hoag: Older lady sitting in rocking chair], 4
    - [Marhsall Hoag: Older lady standing in front of fireplace], 5
    - [Marshall Hoag: Older lady sitting in rocking chair], 6
    - [Marshall Hoag: Older lady standing in front of window], 7
  - President Herbert Hoover and Lowell Thomas, circa 1950s; 25 (Box 1614)
    - [President Herbert Hoover sitting at table with Lowell Thomas], 1
    - [President Herbert Hoover sitting next to Lowell Thomas], 2
  - Illinois Institute of Technology (Doctor Henry T. Heald Award), 1978 - 1981; 26 (Box 1614)
    - The Dr. Henry T. Heald Award; Established in 1977 Illinois Institute of Technology Chicago, Illinois, 1
    - Verso: The Dr. Henry T. Heald Award; Established in 1977 Illinois Institute of Technology Chicago, Illinois, 1-verso
  - Irving retirement dinner [color photographs], undated; 27 (Box 1614)
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Two men talking], 1
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Group of people talking], 2
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Group of people talking], 3
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Group of people], 4
    - [Irving retirement dinner: People sitting down at dining tables], 5
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Group of people talking], 6
    - [Irving retirement dinner: People sitting at dining table], 7
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Woman and man standing behind cake and flowers], 8
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Man and woman standing, people clapping], 9
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Lowell Thomas handing a gift to a man], 10
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Man cutting cake], 11
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Man and woman standing behind cake and flowers], 12
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Man standing behind table], 13
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Older man standing against wall], 14
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Older man talking], 15
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Group of women talking], 16
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Lowell Thomas standing], 17
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Two women and two men conversing], 18
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Group of people talking], 19
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Cake that reads "Good Luck, Ruth and Ira], 20
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Set dining table], 21
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Man talking to two women], 22
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Set dining table], 23
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Man talking to two women], 24
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Man talking to a woman], 25
    - [Irving retirement dinner: Two men and two women talking], 26
    - [Irving retirement dinner: People sitting at dining table], 27
  - John Jay, 1944, 1971; 28 (Box 1614)
    - Happy Holidays, 1
    - Verso: Great to see you both at the Harvard Club and sorry about the chaos-glad Princeton came thru, 1-verso
    - Season's Greetings from Lois, Johnny and John Jr. (also Pepi), 2
    - Verso: So enjoyed seeing you this fall-+ so sorry we had to cancel that Alaska trip, 2-verso
    - Season's Greetings from Lois, Johnny, Surrey, John and Pogo, 3
    - Verso: See you at Sun Valley? New show going great guns!..., 3-verso
    - Season's Greetings from Johnny, Lois, John and Surrey, 4
    - Enjoyed our weekend with you both so much! And delighted to hear you are on the [?] Skibob Team, 4-verso
    - Photo by John Jay Turin, Italy, 5
    - Verso: Photo by John Jay Turin, Italy, 5-verso
  - Sheila Jenness, undated; 29 (Box 1614)
    - Sheila Jenness, 1
    - Verso: Sheila Jenness [address] CO 5-9207 CO 5-9209, 1-verso
    - Sheila Jenness, 2
    - Verso: Sheila Jenness [address], 2-verso
  - Kaiser-Frazer Sales Corporation, 1953 - 1954; 30 (Box 1614)
    - From Willow Cottage, Kaiser-Frazer's drive-away cottage at Willow Run,--all roads lead to new adventure in motoring thrills., 1
    - Verso: From Willow Cottage, Kaiser-Frazer's drive-away cottage at Willow Run,--all roads lead to new adventure in motoring thrills., 1-verso
    - [Kaiser-Frazer Sales Corporation: Lowell Thomas speaking on stage], 2
    - Verso: Kaiser file, 2-verso
  - Knickerbocker Greys, 1938; 31 (Box 1614)
    - [Knickerbocker Greys: Men in uniform], 1
    - [Knickerbocker Greys: Lowell Thomas talking to a man in uniform], 2
  - Lowell Thomas Kemp, undated; 32 (Box 1614)
    - VandenBerg-Hillsdale Caption: Sincerely Lowell Thomas Kemp, 1
  - Captain Knight, 1936; 33 (Box 1614)
    - Capt. C.W.R. Knight, 1
    - Verso: Capt. C.W.R. Knight, 1-verso
    - Capt. C.W.R. Knight, 2
    - Verso: Capt. C.W.R. Knight, 2-verso
    - Capt. C.W.R. Knight, 3
    - Verso: Capt. C.W.R. Knight, 3-verso
    - Capt. C.W.R. Knight, 4
    - Verso: Capt. C.W.R. Knight, 4-verso
  - Robert Kuck [color photographs], 1976 - 1978; 34 (Box 1614)
    - [Robert Kuck: Portrait of a woman], 1
    - [Robert Kuck: Man holding dog], 2
    - [Robert Kuck: Portrait of man], 3
  - Otto Lang [includes color photographs], 1978; 35 (Box 1614)
    - [Otto Lang: Lowell Thomas and man standing next to "Alf Ingen Ski School" sign], 1
    - [Otto Lang: Lowell Thomas with three other men in next to "Alf Ingen Ski School" sign], 2
    - [Otto Lang:] L.T. looking keenly at distant horizons! (Ladakm---Mebbe???), 3
    - Verso: L.T. looking keenly at distant horizons! (Ladakm---Mebbe???), 3-verso
    - [Otto Lang: Lowell Thomas with three other men next to "Alf Ingen Ski School" sign], 4
    - "Our" Fearless Leader., 5
    - Verso: "Our" Fearless Leader., 5-verso
    - Our "Happy Warrior.", 6
    - Verso: Our "Happy Warrior.", 6-verso
    - *** I like!!!, 7
    - Verso: *** I like!!!, 7-verso
    - [Otto Lang: Lowell Thomas and another man on skiis], 8
    - Dear Lowell: It is really so enormously nice of you to keep Peter in mind AIFT is both a wonderful idea + schooling + future, 9
    - Verso: Dear Lowell: It is really so enormously nice of you to keep Peter in mind AIFT is both a wonderful idea + schooling + future, 9-verso
  - Reverend Ralph C. Lankler - Christ Church, undated; 36 (Box 1614)
    - Caption: Rev. Dr. Ralph C. Lankler, 1
  - Lectures, 1942; 37 (Box 1614)
    - [Lectures: Man working with metal], 1
    - [Lectures: Group of men holding a sign that reads "45th Congress of American Industry Honors Three-Generation Employees of Henry Disston & Sons - At New York City Luncheon], 2
  - Legion of Valor, circa 1918; 38 (Box 1614)
    - Bosch Alherlinr [?] Lt Allen [?], 1
    - Verso: Bosch Alherlinr [?] Lt Allen [?], 1-verso
  - Liars Club Contest, 1939; 39 (Box 1614)
    - Harry J. McGowan; Civil Engineer Signs - Violin Instruction; Wyncote, Penna-, 1
    - Note[PDF]: Wyncote, Penna; Dec. 28, 1939, Sun Oil Co. Liar; Mr. Lowell Thomas; Sunoco Oil Co- New York; Herewith file application for Candidacy of "Big Liar" to wit, 2
  - Libbey-Owens-Ford Co. [color photographs], 1969 May 29 - June 12; 40 (Box 1614)
    - [Libbey-Owens-Ford Co.: Lowell Thomas standing in white room], 1
    - [Libbey-Owens-Ford Co.: Lowell Thomas standing in white room], 2
    - [Libbey-Owens-Ford Co.: Lowell Thomas standing in white room], 3
    - [Libbey-Owens-Ford Co.: Lowell Thomas standing in white room], 4
  - Log houses, 1967; 41 (Box 1614)
    - [no description], 1
  - Lowell Thomas Remembers - The Movietone Library, 1970s; 42 (Box 1614)
    - PBS Lowell Thomas is host for LOWELL THOMAS REMEMBERS on PBS, ______ at ______ on Channel _____. The voice of Movietone News for many years, 1
    - PBS Lowell Thomas is host for LOWELL THOMAS REMEMBERS on PBS, ______ at ______ on Channel _____. The voice of Movietone News for many years, 2
    - PBS Lowell Thomas is host for LOWELL THOMAS REMEMBERS on PBS, ______ at ______ on Channel _____. The voice of Movietone News for many years, 3
    - PBS Lowell Thomas, of LOWELL THOMAS REMEMBERS on PBS, ______ at ______ on Channel _____ recalls vividly the events of the years 1919-1963, 4
    - PBS Lowell Thomas, of LOWELL THOMAS REMEMBERS on PBS, ______ at ______ on Channel _____ recalls vividly the events of the years 1919-1963, 5
    - PBS Lowell Thomas, of LOWELL THOMAS REMEMBERS on PBS, ______ at ______ on Channel _____ recalls vividly the events of the years 1919-1963, 6
    - Lowell Thomas, host for LOWELL THOMAS REMEMBERS on PBS, will share his memories of the years 1919-1963 in a 44-part series, 7
    - Lowell Thomas, host for LOWELL THOMAS REMEMBERS on PBS, will share his memories of the years 1919-1963 in a 44-part series, 8
    - Lowell Thomas, host for LOWELL THOMAS REMEMBERS on PBS, will share his memories of the years 1919-1963 in a 44-part series, 9
  - L - miscellaneous, 1962; 43 (Box 1614)
    - Dan Latter, 1
    - Verso: Dan Latter, 1-verso
  Box 1615
- Topical files 1, 2.1.9.4
  - Macalester College (Kathleen Austin), 1958; 1 (Box 1615)
    - To Mr. Lowell Thomas; In thanks for the scholarship from Kathleen Austin, 1
    - Verso: To Mr. Lowell Thomas; In thanks for the scholarship from Kathleen Austin, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of 5] Maclaester College; Box 52; March 16, 1958; Dear Mr. Thomas, Last fall when Dean Mousalite told me I had been selected as one of the students to receive the Lowell Thomas Endowed Scholarship, 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of 5], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3 of 5], 4
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 4 of 5], 5
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 5 of 5], 6
  - Donald MacMillan, circa 1964; 2 (Box 1615)
    - [Donald Macmillan: Portrait of a captain], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of 2] Mrs. Donald B. MacMillan - Provincetown, Massachusetts; September 14, 1964; Dear Lowell: We don't know where you and Fran are these days but we think of you both often, 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of 2], 3
    - Note: Ed Morse took this poliroid color shot - not good..., 4
    - Note: [envelope], 5
  - Miriam MacMillan [color photographs], 1980; 3 (Box 1615)
    - [Woman (Miriam Macmillan?) in graduation cap and gown], 1
    - [Woman (Miriam Macmillan?) in graduating gown with three other people in graduating gowns], 2
  - Maine Lumberjacks, 1938 - 1940; 4 (Box 1615)
    - The Maine Lumberjacks, 1
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Man standing on box singing with a band behind him], 2
    - Verso: Same size as on raft., 2-verso
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Men cutting a tree], 3
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Men cutting a tree], 4
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Band playing on dock], 5
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Men standing outside of tent], 6
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Reindeer pulling sleds], 7
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Reindeer pulling sleds], 8
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Reindeer pulling sleds by snowy mountain], 9
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Man on skiis], 10
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Man on skiis, Reindeer pulling sleds], 11
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Sleds and reindeer], 12
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Reindeer], 13
    - Egavik, Alaska., 14
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Reindeer lined up], 15
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks:] Moving Camp, 16
    - Verso: Moving Camp, 16-verso
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks:] Hershel Island, 17
    - Verso: Hershel Island, 17-verso
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks:] Hershel Island, 18
    - Verso: Hershel Island, 18-verso
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Vast land], 19
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks:] Camp at King Point, 20
    - Verso: Camp at King Point, 20-verso
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks:] 3 Lap Herders at Camp, 21
    - Verso: 3 Lap Herders at Camp, 21-verso
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks:] Camp on [?] River, 22
    - Verso: Camp on [?] River, 22-verso
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Reindeer], 23
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Vast land, Reindeer], 24
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Vast land, Reindeer], 25